<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dessert on This is Wei</title>
    <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/tags/dessert/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dessert on This is Wei</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 12:16:35 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/tags/dessert/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheesecakes</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-30-cheesecakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-30-cheesecakes/</guid>
      <description>Here is my rating of the New York Style Cheesecake that I had so far in my life:
No. 1 Two Little Red Hens has been listed as the No. 1 dessert spot in NYC. It is located right next to Heidelberg Restaurant. Before visiting this place, my number one choice was Junior&amp;rsquo;s. After had the cheesecake from Two Little Red Hens, I would say this became my favorite cheesecake shop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Anniversary</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-30-our-anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-30-our-anniversary/</guid>
      <description>My husband and I like to do things out of ordinary on our anniversaries. Last year, we went to the New Fulton Fish Market, which we had to stay up late for. This year, we decided to do a self-guided bike tour around Manhattan.
We started out from the west village by having the breakfast at The Butcher&amp;rsquo;s Daughter, which both us wanted to try for a while. I ordered matcha green tea pancake and my husband got the butcher&amp;rsquo;s omelette.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philippine Food Feast</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-26-philippine-food-feast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-26-philippine-food-feast/</guid>
      <description>I am always a big fan of Philippine cuisine, which has similar flavor as Chinese, Spanish and Malaysian cuisines. Dishes ranges from fried fish, whole roasted pig to halo-halo. Since our car maintenance place, Firestone Complete Auto Care, is very close to Journal Square in Jersey City, my husband and I always stop by at least one Filipino restaurant while waiting.
Our usual go-to-spot is Philippine Bread House. There are actually two separate restaurants/shops in the store front.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 Partial Solar Eclipse NYC</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-21-solar-eclipse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-21-solar-eclipse/</guid>
      <description>It has been years since the last time that I saw a partial solar eclipse in China. I remembered to look out the window of a 6-floor apartment building in an open area was pretty awesome. Plus- there had no clouds on that day- which was very rare in my hometown. The entire process didn&amp;rsquo;t last that long but enough for me to enjoy.
Today- I was able to see the partial solar eclipse again in NYC.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>