<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cake on This is Wei</title>
    <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/tags/cake/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cake on This is Wei</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>© 2020 thisiswei</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 12:16:35 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/tags/cake/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Before and after Christmas 2017</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-12-26-chrismas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-12-26-chrismas/</guid>
      <description>This year, we started the Christmas celebration by checking off one of the wish-to-try places from our list. I would say overall, I had a SUPER fatty Christmas!
The Atlantic Chipshop was one of the places that I wanted to try for a long time. Can&amp;rsquo;t believe that the original location was closed a few years ago and I have never been there. I heard of this place from a coworker and he said that they deep fry everything here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebration</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-12-16-special-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-12-16-special-day/</guid>
      <description>Today was another special day! We have started the week-long celebration a few days before the actual day, so we were able to visit more places!
Mont Blanc 52 was recommended by my husband&amp;rsquo;s best friend. WARNING: melting cheese smells funky. We started with some house salad with light dressing. We shared lightly fried calamari and escargots. The garlic butter where escargots swam in was remarkable! I dipped bread in it after finishing escargots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philippine Food Feast</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-26-philippine-food-feast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-26-philippine-food-feast/</guid>
      <description>I am always a big fan of Philippine cuisine, which has similar flavor as Chinese, Spanish and Malaysian cuisines. Dishes ranges from fried fish, whole roasted pig to halo-halo. Since our car maintenance place, Firestone Complete Auto Care, is very close to Journal Square in Jersey City, my husband and I always stop by at least one Filipino restaurant while waiting.
Our usual go-to-spot is Philippine Bread House. There are actually two separate restaurants/shops in the store front.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>