<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on This is Wei</title>
    <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on This is Wei</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 12:16:35 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cupcakes</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-10-09-cupcakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-10-09-cupcakes/</guid>
      <description>Cupcakes are normally not my go-to choices for dessert. I still do have my favorite cupcake spots.
Two Little Red Hens has been listed as the No. 1 dessert spot in NYC. This place not only offers great cheesecakes but also awesome cupcakes. We couldn&amp;rsquo;t have enough of the cupcake with the mini yellow cupcake with Swiss vanilla buttercream. We got a regular sized one in additional. As they advertised, it was silky smooth and not too sweet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soup Dumplings</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-09-30-soup-dumplings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-09-30-soup-dumplings/</guid>
      <description>There are so many good soup dumpling (Xiaolongbao/小籠包) places in the world. The most well known one must be Din Tai Fung/鼎泰豐. Since Din Tai Fung has not yet entered the New York market, I have tried many other great soup dumplings in the area. And yes, I did have Din Tai Fung.
Shanghai Asian Manor is my favorite place to get soup dumplings. They were much better than Din Tai Fung.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northern Jersey Diners</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-09-16-northern-jersey-diners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-09-16-northern-jersey-diners/</guid>
      <description>New Jersey has the most diners in the world and is sometimes referred to as the diner capital of the world. - New Jersey Facts and Trivia from 50states.com.
Here are some diners which I have visited often in the Northern Jersey.
Tops Diner is voted to be the best diner in America, accordingly to Time Out. I feel very lucky to live not too far from here. I did had a bad experience during my first visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asian Influenced Cheesecakes</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-09-04-asianinfluencedcheesecakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-09-04-asianinfluencedcheesecakes/</guid>
      <description>Here is my rating of Asian influenced cheesecakes that I had so far in my life:
No. 1 Komegash Too is located in Newport Jersey City, which is the only Japanese restaurant in the area. I used to go here quite often. They serve Lady M cheesecake with fresh fruits, cream and mint leaves. The cheesecake is light and fluffy.
 
 No. 2 Ootoya has been one of my favorite lunch spot near Flatiron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheesecakes at Restaurants</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-09-04-cheesecakesatrestaurants/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-09-04-cheesecakesatrestaurants/</guid>
      <description>Here is my rating of the cheesecakes, which are served as a dessert item, at a restaurant that I had so far in my life:
Steakhouses No. 1 Peter Luger is the most a New York steakhouse can get. Their porterhouse is definitely out of the world. Cheese cake and Schlag add a great ending to the meal.
 
 No. 2 The Capital Grille in FiDi is my top spot for having the restaurant week lunches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Style Cheesecakes</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-30-nystylecheesecakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-30-nystylecheesecakes/</guid>
      <description>Here is my rating of the New York Style Cheesecake from a bakery that I had so far in my life:
No. 1 Two Little Red Hens has been listed as the No. 1 dessert spot in NYC. It is located right next to Heidelberg Restaurant. Before visiting this place, my number one choice was Junior&amp;rsquo;s. After had the cheesecake from Two Little Red Hens, I would say this became my favorite cheesecake shop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Anniversary</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-30-our-anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-30-our-anniversary/</guid>
      <description>My husband and I like to do things out of ordinary on our anniversaries. Last year, we went to the New Fulton Fish Market, which we had to stay up late for. This year, we decided to do a self-guided bike tour around Manhattan.
We started out from the west village by having the breakfast at The Butcher&amp;rsquo;s Daughter, which both us wanted to try for a while. I ordered matcha green tea pancake and my husband got the butcher&amp;rsquo;s omelette.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philippine Food Feast</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-26-philippine-food-feast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-26-philippine-food-feast/</guid>
      <description>I am always a big fan of Philippine cuisine, which has similar flavor as Chinese, Spanish and Malaysian cuisines. Dishes ranges from fried fish, whole roasted pig to halo-halo. Since our car maintenance place, Firestone Complete Auto Care, is very close to Journal Square in Jersey City, my husband and I always stop by at least one Filipino restaurant while waiting.
Our usual go-to-spot is Philippine Bread House. There are actually two separate restaurants/shops in the store front.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 Partial Solar Eclipse NYC</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-21-solar-eclipse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-21-solar-eclipse/</guid>
      <description>It has been years since the last time that I saw a partial solar eclipse in China. I remembered to look out the window of a 6-floor apartment building in an open area was pretty awesome. Plus, there had no clouds on that day, which was very rare in my hometown. The entire process didn&amp;rsquo;t last that long but enough for me to enjoy.
Today, I was able to see the partial solar eclipse again in NYC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiking along the Hudson</title>
      <link>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-18-hiking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 12:16:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weivayn.github.io/thisiswei/posts/2017-08-18-hiking/</guid>
      <description>It was a very nice day today. After waking up, my husband and I decided to go for a hike along the Hudson River. We found Carpenters&amp;rsquo; Trail, which was about 4 miles with a great view of the city.
We started our trip by stopping at this Starbucks. I got a cool lime refresher, which was very refreshing for a hot summer day.
  
 We started the hike from the parking area (TIPS: there was a $5 fee for parking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>